Open the project, you can see that there are some different shapes and properties of some panels.
The particles are also a little different.
First, let's simulate the bottom row of the panels.
You can see that the wrinkles of the panels are different.
The wrinkles of the first row are larger, and the wrinkles of the second row are darker.
The wrinkles of the second row are more detailed.
The wrinkles of the third row are more delicate, and the wrinkles of the third row are softer.
Click to see that the properties of each panel are the same, except that the particles of the last panel are smaller.
The additional priced space which is more
and very wonderful one.
The top and bottom of the pleats are also very different, and not the same pleats.
The last version has more pleats, so the pleats look more detailed.
And the main difference is that the main difference is not very big.
In general, the pleats of the triangular and quadrilateral mesh are harder,
and the pleats of the vertical mesh are more delicate.
Next, let's take a look at the simulation of the different pleats.
Since the pleats are smaller, I will try to switch to GPU simulation.
From left to right, the pleats are gradually reduced.
The pleats are gradually reduced.
After starting the simulation, you can see that the pleats of the largest diameter have already been simulated.
The pleats of the smallest diameter have just begun to be simulated.
Since there are only one or two pleats now, the bundled pleats that are not already done can be simulated.
The07.
There are units which are not fully simulated.
That is, month of the lifestyle.
The speed will be slower when the particle diameter is reduced to 3, and there are too many unnecessary wrinkles.
Therefore, it is recommended that you reduce the particle diameter to 10 to 5 in the usual production process.
In addition, the fabric of the panel will also affect the simulation effect.
First of all, you can see that because it is a fan-shaped panel,
the length of the two panels is not much different.
Therefore, there is no wrinkle at the seam side.
Secondly, the difference between the two panels is relatively large.
The second panel is obviously softer and has a more vertical feel.
This is because the two panels use different fabrics.
The second panel uses the same fabric.
Clicking on the fabric to check its physical properties,
you can see that the strength of the gold-plated sand and the strength of the diagonal line are relatively low.
you can count on the eyes for both.
This is because the fabric is very smooth.
It's easy to take out thezenified faults and make err for longer.
The second and third panels are Hostes of Perspective.
This is the singsion position that can also be acted to be straight after the insole is prepared.
We can see their feet are more harm than one.
If you take a closer look at the sill area,
You can see the direction of the texture of each panel, and the arrow symbolizes the gold image.
You can see the texture of the longer part of the click.
The shorter part is more like the gold image or the tail image.
Click on the physical properties of the fabric, you can see that the feature of the fabric is that it is very easy to stretch.
In comparison, because the strength of the sand is high, it is more vertical, but the direction of the foot line is more vertical.
The main reasons for affecting the shape of the pleats are the arrangement of the grid, the ratio of particles, the properties of the fabric, and the shape of the panel.
Next, I would like to show you the pleating effect of different panels.
First, I would like to show you the pleating effect of rectangular panels.
You can see that there is only a difference in the width of the rectangular panels from left to right.
The number of pleats in this panel is the same.
Therefore, from the seam side, there is a large amount of pleats, and then it gradually becomes smaller and wider.
When the panel is bigger, the pleats on the seam side become more and the pleats on the whole become narrower.
Compared to the original panel, the pleats are also very different in shape.
From the bottom, the size of the pleats is not much different, but the number of pleats is more.
Then let's take a look at the simulation effect of these fan-shaped panels in the middle.
You can see that these panels have an additional triangle in the rectangular shape.
In this way, the length of the pleats is the same.
Let's adjust the position of the panel a little bit to facilitate our simulation.
After opening the simulation, we can see that the shape of the panel is very different from the rectangular shape.
First of all, the shape of the pleats is more regular.
A triangle will form a pleat.
The rectangular part of the panel is more even, and the seam side is also more even.
If you want to create such a panel, you can use the extension tool to create it.
Select the extension tool, set the direction of the baseline line, and immediately open the panel.
Close the panel, this way the panel can be easily seen in the scene.
Open the panel.
Then open the panel.
Close the panel.
Open the panel.
The size of the panel will also affect the fold effect of the model.
From this side, the fold is not too bad.
From the bottom, you can clearly see that the fold is getting bigger and wider.
And from this side, the panel looks bigger and wider.
Therefore, this kind of panel is suitable for making some upper panels,
but the bottom is very white and has a very loose structure.
If you look at some of the other models,
you can see that the bigger the panel, the more folds, and the more creases.
For this kind of panel, which is getting shorter and shorter,
but has a lot of folds,
you will need to use a spiral panel.